Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Here.
هنا.
Where do you think you're going?
إلى أين تعتقد أنك ذاهب؟
Dare to ruin my plans, huh?
هل تجرؤ على تدمير خططي، أليس كذلك؟
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
You want to catch me? No way!
هل تريد أن تمسك بي؟ لا يمكن!
Not good.
ليس جيدا.
Burning this much Ancestral Hemp releases deadly poison.
حرق هذه الكمية من القنب الأصلي يطلق سمًا قاتلًا.
Go, let's get out first.
اذهب، دعنا نخرج أولاً.
Go!
يذهب!
That was really close.
لقد كان ذلك قريبًا جدًا.
Yuniang has escaped.
لقد هرب يونيانغ.
How will we explain this to the City Lord?
كيف سنشرح هذا الأمر لسيد المدينة؟
The Eldest Young Master's faction
فصيل السيد الشاب الأكبر
has been waiting for a chance to harm you.
لقد كان ينتظر فرصة لإيذائك.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
I'll get the best doctor for you.
سأحضر لك أفضل طبيب.
You'll surely recover.
سوف تتعافى بالتأكيد.
I'm afraid I won't make it.
أخشى أنني لن أتمكن من ذلك.
Hunchback.
أحدب.
You're an important witness.
أنت شاهد مهم.
You must stay alive.
يجب عليك البقاء على قيد الحياة.
To prove our Young Master's innocence.
لإثبات براءة سيدنا الشاب.
Zhusheng, life comes first.
تشوشينغ، الحياة تأتي أولاً.
Hunchback.
أحدب.
Have you ever seen the real owner of this inn?
هل سبق لك أن رأيت المالك الحقيقي لهذا النزل؟
The owner is very mysterious.
المالك غامض للغاية.
We low-ranking attendants
نحن المرافقين ذوي الرتبة المنخفضة
have never seen him.
لم أره قط.
But I've heard
ولكنني سمعت
on the first and fifteenth
في اليوم الأول والخامس عشر
he always comes to check the accounts and collect money.
يأتي دائمًا للتحقق من الحسابات وجمع الأموال.
Only
فقط
Awu can actually meet him.
أوو يمكن أن تقابله فعليا.
Master's Wife, do you remember anything?
زوجة السيد هل تتذكرين شيئا؟
She's been drugged for a long time.
لقد تم تخديرها لفترة طويلة.
Her meridians are sealed.
خطوط الطول لها مختومة.
It'll be hard for her to regain consciousness soon.
سيكون من الصعب عليها استعادة وعيها قريبًا.
I fear I'll die here today.
أخشى أن أموت هنا اليوم.
I'm neither human nor ghost now.
أنا لست إنسانًا ولا شبحًا الآن.
Living has no meaning.
ليس للعيش معنى.
But dying won't be in vain.
ولكن الموت لن يذهب سدى.
Second Young Master.
الشاب الثاني.
You must find the mastermind behind all this.
يجب عليك أن تجد العقل المدبر وراء كل هذا.
Avenge us.
انتقم لنا.
Too rude.
وقح جداً.
That Second Young Master and his people are really too rough.
إن ذلك الشاب الثاني وشعبه قاسيون للغاية.
What's the point of trying so hard?
ما الهدف من المحاولة بكل هذا الجهد؟
In the end, it's all for nothing.
في النهاية، كل هذا بلا فائدة.
Eldest Young Master.
السيد الشاب الأكبر.
You are our future true emperor.
أنت إمبراطورنا الحقيقي في المستقبل.
Even Heaven is on your side.
حتى الجنة بجانبك .
Of course.
بالطبع.
Who's the cook today?
من هو الطباخ اليوم؟
Why didn't you clean the meat thoroughly for me?
لماذا لم تنظفي اللحم جيدا؟
Royal Father is the most frugal.
الأب الملكي هو الأكثر اقتصادا.
As the eldest son,
باعتباري الابن الأكبر،
I must set an example.
يجب أن أكون قدوة.
Diligence and thrift are the way.
الاجتهاد والاقتصاد هما الطريق.
You—
أنت-
Aren't you putting me in a bad position?
ألا تضعني في موقف سيء؟
Can't even handle such a small task.
لا أستطيع حتى التعامل مع مثل هذه المهمة الصغيرة.
Useless to keep you.
لا فائدة من الاحتفاظ بك.
Yes, Young Master.
نعم سيدي الشاب.
Rest assured, Young Master.
اطمئن يا سيدي الشاب.
Yuniang burned the inn thoroughly.
أحرق يونيانغ النزل بالكامل.
They'll never find this place.
لن يجدوا هذا المكان أبدًا.
Wasn't Minister Hu
ألم يكن الوزير هو؟
killed not far from the inn?
قتل ليس ببعيد عن النزل؟
I suppose
أفترض
they used this as an excuse
لقد استخدموا هذا كذريعة
to give the Second Young Master a chance.
لإعطاء الفرصة للشاب الثاني.
Eldest Young Master, you're wise.
أيها السيد الشاب الأكبر، أنت حكيم.
Two sorcerers suddenly came to the inn today.
فجأة جاء ساحران إلى النزل اليوم.
They must be with the Second Young Master.
يجب أن يكونوا مع الشاب الثاني.
They worked together inside and out.
لقد عملوا معًا في الداخل والخارج.
They destroyed our secret room.
لقد دمروا غرفتنا السرية.
It was definitely premeditated.
لقد كان ذلك متعمدا بالتأكيد.
Yuniang barely escaped with her life.
تمكنت يونيانغ من النجاة بحياتها بصعوبة.
That Dongqing
أن دونغ تشينغ
Why is he mixed up with the Second Young Master too?
لماذا هو مختلط مع الشاب الثاني أيضا؟
So, Young Master,
إذن، أيها السيد الشاب،
what should we do now?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل الآن؟
It must be truly cleaned up.
يجب أن يتم تنظيفه حقا.
Thoroughly cleaned.
تم تنظيفها جيدا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Royal Father
الأب الملكي
The name of Hu Shangshu
اسم هو شانغشو
also appears in the ledger
يظهر أيضًا في دفتر الأستاذ
He must be a regular at this inn
لا بد أنه من رواد هذا النزل بشكل منتظم
Although the cause of death is still unclear
على الرغم من أن سبب الوفاة لا يزال غير واضح
it is definitely connected to the inn
إنه مرتبط بالتأكيد بالنزل
The person behind this has sinister intentions
الشخص الذي يقف وراء هذا لديه نوايا شريرة
On one hand
من ناحية أخرى
they use the Beast-Creation Art to amass wealth
إنهم يستخدمون فن خلق الوحوش لجمع الثروة
On the other hand
على الجانب الآخر
they also create those fake humans
كما أنهم يخلقون هؤلاء البشر المزيفين
deliberately sabotaging the Fire Worship Festival
تخريب مهرجان عبادة النار عمدًا
You mean
هل تقصد
the disaster at this Fire Worship Festival
الكارثة في مهرجان عبادة النار هذا
was caused by human hands
كان سببه أيدي البشر
That's right
هذا صحيح
On the day of the Fire Worship Festival
في يوم عيد عبادة النار
we found on those fake corrupted bodies
لقد وجدنا على تلك الجثث الفاسدة المزيفة
this as well
هذا أيضا
Ancestral Hemp
القنب الأجداد
This is the substance that destroys people
هذه هي المادة التي تدمر الناس
Ancestral Hemp is extremely potent
القنب الأصلي قوي للغاية
It is strictly forbidden to cultivate it in Xuan City
يُمنع منعًا باتًا زراعته في مدينة شوان
Even inhaling a little after burning
حتى استنشاق القليل بعد الحرق
will seize one's mind
سوف يستولي على عقله
Any other use must be reported through proper channels
يجب الإبلاغ عن أي استخدام آخر من خلال القنوات المناسبة
Only with Royal Father's approval can it enter the city
لا يمكن دخول المدينة إلا بموافقة الأب الملكي
Buying or using it privately is a serious crime
إن شرائه أو استخدامه بشكل خاص يعد جريمة خطيرة
And this herb is extremely expensive
وهذه العشبة غالية الثمن للغاية
Just one qian
تشيان واحد فقط
costs five taels of silver
تكلف خمسة تايلات من الفضة
All these herbs in the room
كل هذه الأعشاب في الغرفة
Whoever has the courage and ability
من لديه الشجاعة والقدرة
to do such things
القيام بمثل هذه الأشياء
must have an unusual status
يجب أن يكون له وضع غير عادي
No matter who it is
لا يهم من هو
I will show no mercy
لن أظهر أي رحمة
Master's Wife, you are truly impressive
زوجة السيد، أنت مثيرة للإعجاب حقًا
Even with ten silver needles sealing your acupoints
حتى مع وجود عشر إبر فضية تغلق نقاط الوخز بالإبر لديك
you still have such skills
لا تزال لديك مثل هذه المهارات
You really are tough
أنت حقا قوي
Senior Brother
الأخ الأكبر
Did she remember something?
هل تذكرت شيئا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
The matter between your master and me
الأمر بيني وبين سيدك
You don't support it either?
أنت لا تؤيد ذلك أيضًا؟
We support it
نحن ندعمه
Of course we do
بالطبع نفعل
You and my master
أنت وسيدي
are a perfect match
هم تطابق مثالي
born to be together
ولدنا لنكون معًا
Yes, yes
نعم نعم
Yes
نعم
Tell us about the two of you
أخبرنا عنكما
I want to hear it
أريد أن أسمعها
Well
حسنًا
Master's Wife, to be honest
زوجة السيد، لأكون صادقا
You and my master are elders
أنت وسيدي شيخان
As juniors
كصغار
it's not proper for us to ask
ليس من المناسب لنا أن نسأل
But then again
ولكن مرة أخرى
once we find Master
بمجرد أن نجد السيد
he can tell you in person
يمكنه أن يخبرك شخصيا
and everything will be clear
وسيكون كل شيء واضحا
Yes, yes
نعم نعم
The medicine is here
الدواء هنا
Master's Wife, it's time for your medicine
زوجة السيد، حان وقت دوائك
Master Bukku is really something
المعلم بوكو هو حقا شيء
He is famous in the martial world
وهو مشهور في عالم القتال
and won the beauty's heart
وفاز بقلب الجميلة
It's truly enviable
إنه أمر مثير للحسد حقا
You, young Master's Wife
أنتِ زوجة السيد الشاب
have quite a bold taste
لديها طعم جريء للغاية
Watch your words
انتبه لكلماتك
My Master's Wife is beautiful and kind
زوجة سيدي جميلة ولطيفة
just a bit short-tempered
فقط سريع الغضب قليلا
Don't provoke her
لا تستفزها
Yes, yes
نعم نعم
I won't, I won't
لن افعل، لن افعل
I won't
أنا لن
She hasn't yet
لم تفعل ذلك بعد
fully regained her memory
استعادت ذاكرتها بالكامل
Baihui and Fengfu
بايهوي وفنغفو
The silver needles in those two acupoints controlling her mind
الإبر الفضية في هاتين النقطتين تتحكمان في عقلها
haven't been removed yet
لم يتم إزالتها بعد
The legendary poison master Feng Wuzhou
سيد السم الأسطوري فينغ ووتشو
How did she end up like this?
كيف انتهى بها الأمر هكذا؟
We'll have to wait until she's stable
علينا أن ننتظر حتى تستقر حالتها
to find out
لمعرفة ذلك
Did you see clearly?
هل رأيت بوضوح؟
Yes, it's her
نعم إنها هي
But she seems to have lost her memory
لكن يبدو أنها فقدت ذاكرتها
What should we do next?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل بعد ذلك؟
Wait and see
انتظر وشاهد
Royal Father actually claimed illness to keep me out.
في الواقع ادعى والدي الملكي المرض لإبقائي خارجًا.
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
Be careful, Eldest Prince.
كن حذرا، أيها الأمير الأكبر.
My zhiyuan.
تشي يوان الخاص بي.
You damned slave, move aside!
أيها العبد الملعون، تنحّى جانبًا!
Move aside!
تنحى جانبا!
Big brother...
الاخ الاكبر...
Yue'er...
يوير...
You're so reckless these days.
أنت متهور جدًا هذه الأيام.
Royal Father should've
كان ينبغي للأب الملكي
married you off to anyone by now.
لقد زوجتك لأي شخص الآن.
So you wouldn't be an eyesore like your lowly birth mother.
حتى لا تكون قبيح المنظر مثل والدتك المتواضعة.
You're such an eyesore.
أنت حقا قبيح المنظر.
Yue'er.
يوير.
You like this zhiyuan?
هل يعجبك هذا zhiyuan؟
I do.
أفعل.
I'll make you like it, make you like it!
سأجعلك تحبه، سأجعلك تحبه!
Like it! Like it!
اعجبني! اعجبني!
You jinx.
أنت نحس.
Even if you fly to the sky,
حتى لو طرت نحو السماء،
when you fall,
عندما تسقط
you'll shatter into pieces.
سوف تتحطم إلى قطع.
Like it.
أعجبني.
Like it! Like it!
اعجبني! اعجبني!
I'll make you like it.
سأجعلك تحبه.
You're the princess of Xuan City.
أنت أميرة مدينة شوان.
If you truly like zhiyuan,
إذا كنت تحب Zhiyuan حقًا،
just tell your father.
فقط أخبر والدك.
All the kites in the city would be yours.
جميع الطائرات الورقية في المدينة ستكون لك.
If anyone
إذا كان أي شخص
tries to bully you with a kite,
يحاول أن يضايقك بطائرة ورقية،
they'll have to ask
سيتعين عليهم أن يسألوا
if my walking cane agrees first.
إذا وافقت عصا المشي الخاصة بي أولاً.
Second Young Master...
الشاب الثاني...
I was just joking.
لقد كنت أمزح فقط.
Why so serious?
لماذا الجدية؟
Right, Yue'er?
صحيح، يوير؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll stab you to death!
سأطعنك حتى الموت!
You're just a mutt born of a woman from Mo City.
أنت مجرد كلب هجين ولد لامرأة من مدينة ميسوري.
No matter how brave you are in battle,
بغض النظر عن مدى شجاعتك في المعركة،
even if you defeated Yao City,
حتى لو هزمت مدينة ياو،
what use are your achievements?
ما فائدة إنجازاتك؟
You're a cripple, yet still so arrogant.
أنت مقعد، ولكنك لا تزال متغطرسًا جدًا.
Hit me! Fight back!
اضربني! قاوم!
If you dare, fight back! Fight back!
إذا تجرأت، قاوم! قاوم!
Fight back!
قاوم!
Eldest Young Master.
السيد الشاب الأكبر.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
The beast-creations we've cultivated
المخلوقات الوحشية التي قمنا بزراعتها
their bodies have started to rot.
بدأت أجسادهم بالتعفن.
There's barely any life left in them.
لم يتبق فيهم أي حياة تقريبًا.
They won't last much longer.
لن يستمروا لفترة أطول.
The Ancestral Hemp in the inn has been burned.
لقد تم حرق القنب القديم في النزل.
There's not much left in the manor either.
لم يتبق الكثير في القصر أيضًا.
If we keep trading with Yao City now,
إذا واصلنا التجارة مع مدينة ياو الآن،
I'm afraid the Second Young Master
أخشى أن يكون الشاب الثاني
will soon trace it back to us.
سيتم إرجاعه إلينا قريبًا.
Second Young Master...
الشاب الثاني...
I know he looks down on me.
أعرف أنه ينظر إلي بازدراء.
They all look down on me.
كلهم ينظرون إليّ بازدراء.
A cripple with a mysterious background.
مقعد ذو خلفية غامضة.
Why should anyone respect me?
لماذا يجب على أي شخص أن يحترمني؟
I'm the eldest legitimate son.
أنا الإبن الشرعي الأكبر.
My mother and my sister
أمي وأختي
are of the highest status.
هم من أعلى مكانة.
No one can compare to me.
لا أحد يستطيع مقارنتي.
Fine.
بخير.
Investigate.
يفتش.
Since you're so eager to die,
لأنك متشوق جدًا للموت،
I'll grant your wish.
سأحقق لك أمنيتك.
Bring it here.
احضره هنا.
Since you resemble my sister
لأنك تشبهين أختي
at least a little,
على الأقل قليلا
I'll be sure to sew you a complete face.
سوف أتأكد من خياطة وجهك بالكامل.
If my sister were here,
لو كانت أختي هنا،
she would understand me and protect me.
إنها سوف تفهمني وتحميني.
This is my sister's favorite red.
هذا هو اللون الأحمر المفضل لأختي.
If you wear it,
إذا كنت ترتديه،
it will surely help make my wishes come true.
وسوف يساعدني بالتأكيد على تحقيق رغباتي.